Do not make such a mistake while making this Kathi Roll.
Today Riya felt like
eating Kathi roll.  So she comes and tells me, Mummy, please
make extra roti.  That's why I
make extra rotis and keep them.  Then I
take two tablespoons of curd, add salt, Kashmiri red
chilli, turmeric and garam masala and
mix it well.  And after adding cheese, I keep it aside to
rest for 10 minutes.  And till then I
cut all the vegetables and
cook them a little in butter.  And if you want, you
can also add onion in it.  Then
add paneer in it and keep it on high flame for 5-10 minutes
so that all its water dries up.  But don't
spend too much on it otherwise all the
cheese will break, which I have already broken.
Then took the roti, applied cream and chutney and
put cheese on top.  Then roasted it a little on the pan.
And when it was given to Riya to eat, she
liked it so much that she finished two rolls.  On
top of that they say,
Mom, please pay back for school also.
And please do tell me in the comments
who likes my recipe?  Radhe Radhe.